<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biometrics by the Botanic Gardens</title>
    <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Biometrics by the Botanic Gardens</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About our speakers</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/speakers/</guid>
      <description>Speaker Profiles Marti Anderson Massey University, New Zealand Distinguished Professor Marti J. Anderson is an ecological statistician whose work spans several disciplines, from ecology to mathematical statistics. A Fellow of the Royal Society of New Zealand, and a recent recipient of a prestigious James Cook Fellowship, she holds the Professorial Chair in Statistics in the New Zealand Institute for Advanced Study (NZIAS) at Massey University in Auckland. Her core research is in community ecology, biodiversity, multivariate analysis, models of ecological count data, experimental design and resampling methods, with a special focus on creating new applied statistics for ecology that can yield new insights into global patterns of biodiversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Venue</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/venue/</guid>
      <description>The University of Adelaide’s National Wine Centre provides important links with the wine industry, is an important platform for wine education and research, and provides a world class venue for food and wine. It contains an interactive permanent exhibition of winemaking, introducing visitors to the technology, varieties and styles of wine. It also has a wine tasting area, giving visitors the opportunity to taste and compare wines from different areas of Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Submission</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/abstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/abstract/</guid>
      <description>Important Dates Abstract submission closes: Extended to 23rd August 2019 Notification of Acceptance: 12th September 2019 Early bird registration closes: 19th September 2019 Registration deadline for presenters: 4th October 2019 Registration closes: 17th November 2019 Conference dates Pre-conference workshops: 1st/2nd December 2019 Conference starts: 3rd December 2019 Conference closes: 6th December 2019 The abstract submission deadline has now passed, however registration for the conference is still open. Please visit the registration page to register now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accomodation</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/accomodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/accomodation/</guid>
      <description>Discounted accomodation for delegates Accomodation at the Ibis Hotel and the Pullman Hotel have special discounted rates of 10% off for delegates of the conference booking between 30th November to 7th December.
To take advantage of this offer, please use the following booking link: Ibis and Pullman discounted rates.
Then
Type Ibis Adelaide or Pullman Adelaide in the destination field. Then select your dates and press search. Should you be asked for your client Business Identification use SCP2258878 and IN232AU632 Other Accomodation options Trip advisor recommends the following near by hotels:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia and New Zealand School Poster competition</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/school-posters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/school-posters/</guid>
      <description>The Australasian Region of the International Biometric Society will hold a special poster competition for year 9 &amp;amp; 10 school students in Australian schools, showcasing statistical methods and explorations of problems related to Biometrics. In Australia, Biometrics is strongly represented through:
Agricultural problems (e.g. agricultural field experiments to examine different types of crops);
The environment and ecology (e.g. understanding causes of air pollution, water pollution; animal movement; pest invasions)
Medicine (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/conduct/</guid>
      <description>IBS-AR Conference Code of Conduct The International Biometric Society Australasian Region (IBS-AR) is dedicated to providing a welcoming and harassment-free experience for everyone. We do not tolerate unprofessional or inappropriate conduct, which includes discrimination and harassment, sexual or otherwise. Conference participants should always work towards maintaining an environment free of harassment and discrimination. At the discretion of the IBS-AR conference organisers and/or IBS-AR council, any participants violating these rules may be asked to leave the conference, without any fee refund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Photos</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/photos/</guid>
      <description>The full collection of photos can be found on the Society Flickr page.
Photos of Venue Venue 01
Venue 02
Venue 03
Venue 04
Venue 05
Venue 06
Venue 07
Venue 08
Venue 09
Venue 10
Venue 11
Venue 12
Venue 13
Venue 14
Venue 15
Venue 16
Venue 17
Venue 18
Venue 19
Venue 20
Venue 21
Venue 22
Tuesday Tuesday 01
Tuesday 02
Tuesday 03
Tuesday 04</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>For further information, please contact us using the form below. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Images of the Wine Tour</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/wine-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/wine-tour/</guid>
      <description>Luxury vineyard touring
Samson tall winery inside
Samson tall winery
Bekkers fine wine
Coast shot
Landrover cube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/media/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People who made this happen</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/acknowledgements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/acknowledgements/</guid>
      <description>Conference Organising Committee Chair of conference organising committee: Prof Alan Welsh
Chair of scientific committee: Dr Petra Kuhnert
Chair of local organising committee: Dr Olena Kravchuk
Treasurer: Mr Warren Muller
Scientific Committee Chair of scientific committee: Dr Petra Kuhnert
Local Organising Committee Chair of local organising committee: Dr Olena Kravchuk
Conference Dinner Organisation: Dr Helena Oakey
Website development: Mr Sam Rogers
Conference Safety Officers Dr Emi Tanaka, Dr Ian Renner and Dr Vanessa Cave</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Titles, Abstracts and Slides</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/talks/</guid>
      <description>The complete book of abstracts can be downloaded here.
TueWedThuFriOpening AddressRoom: Exhibition HallPresenterAbstract TitleTimeSlidesLynette CrockerWelcome to Country8:50 - 9:10Download HereWayne PitchfordConference Opening address9:10 - 9:20Alan WelshPresidental Address9:20 - 9:30Invited Speakers: MedicalRoom: Exhibition HallExpand AllPresenterAbstract TitleTimeSlidesJames CarpenterMultilevel multiple imputation for health and survey data: your flexible (and robust) friend9:30 - 10:30Download HereMultiple imputation is now well established as a practical and flexible method for analyzing partially observed data under the missing at random assumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Details</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/mobile_programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/mobile_programme/</guid>
      <description>SundayMondayTuesdayWednesdayThursdayFridayTimeSunday 1/12/20199:00-10:30Workshops10:30-11:00Morning Tea11:00-12:30Workshops12:30-13:30Lunch13:30-15:30Workshops15:30-16:00Afternoon Tea16:00-17:00WorkshopsTimeMonday 2/12/20199:00-10:30Workshops10:30-11:00Morning Tea11:00-12:30Workshops12:30-13:30Lunch13:30-15:30Workshops15:30-16:00Afternoon Tea16:00-17:00WorkshopsTimeTuesday 3/12/20198:50-9:00Welcome to Country (8:50 - 9:10)
Opening address (9:10 - 9:30)
Room: Exhibition Hall
9:00-9:309:30-10:30Plenary Session (9:30-10:30)
Invited Session (Medical I)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Details</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/programme/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Overview</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/outline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/outline/</guid>
      <description>Conference Program outline For a more mobile-friendly programme, visit mobile programme Venue Map TimeSunday 1/12/2019Monday 2/12/2019Tuesday 3/12/2019Wednesday 4/12/2019Thursday 5/12/2019Friday 6/12/20198:30
Registration desk open8:50-9:00Welcome to Country
Lynette Crocker
(8:50 - 9:10)
Opening address
Prof Wayne Pitchford
(9:10 - 9:20)
Presidential Address
Prof Alan Welsh
(9:20 - 9:30)
Room: Exhibition Hall
Contributed Session (8:50-10:30)Contributed Session (8:50-10:30)JABES/Biometrics Showcase
Chair: Alan Welsh
Room: Exhibition Hall9:00-9:30WorkshopsUniversity of Adelaide North Tce CampusWorkshopsUniversity of Adelaide Waite CampusMethods 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration &amp; Key Dates</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration DatesRegistration opens: 7th June 2019Abstract submission closes: Closed 23rd August 2019Notification of Acceptance: 12th September 2019Early bird registration closes: Closed 27th September 2019Registration deadline for presenters: 4th October 2019Registration closes: 17th November 2019Conference datesPre-conference workshops: 1st/2nd December 2019Conference starts: 3rd December 2019Conference closes: 6th December 2019Conference FeesIBS MemberNon-memberConcessionEarly BirdFull PriceEarly BirdFull PriceFull conference$700$800$800$900$350One Day$350$400$400$450$175Workshops (each)$200$250$100Additional notes: Conference dinner and welcome reception cost included in full conference registration fee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social programme</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/social/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Reception The conference reception will be held from 7pm on Monday 2nd December 2019 at the National Wine Centre (the main conference venue).
Conference Dinner The Biometrics by the Botanic Gardens conference dinner will be held on Thursday 5th December 2019 from 7:30pm at the Adelaide Hills Convention Centre, in Hahndorf.
Transport Busses will leave the National Wine Centre by approximately 7pm on Thursday evening. The dinner venue is about a 30 minute drive into the Adelaide Hills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>The Australasian Region of the International Biometric Society gratefully acknowledges the support offered by the following organisations to the Biometrics by the Botanic Gardens conference.GRDC
CSIRO
University of Adelaide Biometry Hub
ANU
ACEMS
Waite Research Institute
South Australian Health and Medical Research Institute
Australian Grain Technologies
Statistical Society of Australia Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions of Registration</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/conditions/</guid>
      <description>IBS-AR Terms and Conditions of Registration 1. Registration and payment You will be issued a tax invoice once payment has been processed.
You can pay by electronic fund transfer or credit card (MasterCard or Visa only).
No Australian GST is payable as the region is a ‘not-for-profit’ entity with turnover below AU$150,000.
All credit card payments will be processed in Australia using the Australian dollar amount and converted, for delegates outside Australia, to the local currency amount by your financial institution on your card statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/tourism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/tourism/</guid>
      <description>There is something for everyone to see and do in Adelaide and South Australia! Some suggestions are listed below, and for more general information on South Australia including Whale watching, zoos, and festivals, visit the tourism centre, or for more CBD focused attractions, the Adelaide city council provides some good information.
Wine Regions World renowned for it&amp;rsquo;s wine, a visit to SA is not complete without a wine tour. The locations listed below are ordered by driving time from Adelaide CBD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel to and from Adelaide</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/travel/</guid>
      <description>Tips for Adelaide travel To and from the Aiport Adelaide International Aiport is very close to the CBD, and only takes about 20 minutes by car or 35 minutes by bus.
There are numerous options for transport into the CBD from the Airport including:
Taxi Adelaide Metro bus (See below for more details) Car rental Ride sharing Shuttle buses And even bicycle! For further details of these options, see the Adelaide Aiport website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Biometrics?</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/what/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/what/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ausbiometric2019.netlify.app/workshops/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Day 1 - Sunday 1st December 2019 Location Sunday Workshops will be held at the University of Adelaide North Tce Campus. The listings in the location column contain a link to the location of the building on Google maps. A pdf copy of the campus map with room listings is available here. The campus is a short walk from the suggested accomodation options.
Parking There is plenty of parking nearby the University, with much of it having reduced Sunday rates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
